Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trial, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
I'll win, even if he is a captain. I'll win!
The test to see who would fight the Eye of the Midnight Sun was winding down.
There! See? You're getting it now!
The end result was a victory for Yuno, Noelle, and En of Team P.
Then, the identity of the mysterious mage who called himself Xerx was unveiled.
We need your trap magic and your ability to think critically.
The exam is done, and you likely passed. I hope you'll join.
Isn't it time that you wore your robe? The robe of your true squad, Zora Ideale.
Don't know who you're talking about.
Me? I'm just some lame excuse for a super mage who happened to be passing through.
so
.
up
Hey look, Asta isn't budging an inch. He's just like a statue.
Is he still breathing?
Yeah, as far as I can tell. But he isn't himself. Losing the tournament must have hit him really hard.
He seemed awfully busted up over it.
I will catch up to you! I will be the Wizard King! I swear!
I can't blame the poor guy. Not only did his childhood buddy win the whole thing, but I don't think Asta was expecting him to have that much power.
And the shock of being surpassed by his long-standing rival may keep getting worse with every day that passes.
Trust me, I understand the feeling. My sister. My goddess. Marie.
Each day I have to endure without seeing your beautiful smile that damaged my body and soul grows ever deeper.
Forgive me for being so blunt, but I don't think that's the same thing at all.
Hey, I know. Maybe I need to launch a little surprise attack on him.
Nothing cheers a person up like a fun life-or-death battle.
Lightning magic! Thunderbolt destructed!
Don't you dare! Fighting is not going to help Asta right now.
We won't know for sure unless we try!
I think it's safe to assume.
He'll kill him!
Well, if I can't use magic, then can I at least pummel him with a brick?
So not happening.
Come on, Asta. Why are you still sitting here staring into space, huh?
This is because you couldn't go up against that lady killer you know.
It's okay, right, Rouge?
Even if it didn't go quite like you wanted, you did great out there, kiddo.
I'm sure you passed with flying colors.
So give me a big smile, okay, honey?
You better smile or I'm going to make you smile.
What the heck is she trying to do?
That's so nice.
She's acting excessively cheerful in an attempt to bring Asta out of his funk.
Huh?
Yeah, I'm familiar with the tactic.
I act that way on the outside to conceal my sadness when I can't be around Marie.
Well, what are we waiting for, everyone?
We need to follow her lead and be positive.
You're right. That idiot needs a confidence boost.
Oh, nice. So does that mean I can start attacking him now?
What is wrong with you?
What did I just say, luck?
Are you still alive, Asta?
Hey, wait. Isn't it about that time?
To see the Royal Knight Selection Exam results.
They're supposed to be coming here by outpost really soon.
Oh, that's right. Guess it must have slipped my mind.
That outpost should show up any minute now, Asta.
Look, once you make the cut, you're going to catch back up to Mr. Cool in no time.
Then you can leave him in the dust.
I'm not so sure.
Will I even get in?
I mean, I did get eliminated, remember?
Don't sweat the small stuff, sweetie.
She's right. You need to have some more faith in yourself.
But Noelle...
Of course I did win in the finals, so obviously I'm going to be selected for the Royal Knights.
Results like that speak for themselves.
You only won because you were lucky enough to be on the same team as Pretty Boy.
That's still better than you.
Your magic was what caused your team to lose.
I can't believe you would dare to address your superior like that.
Don't talk to me like I'm some clueless rookie.
I am royalty, you know.
And nobody cares, you know.
I feel like that's so old.
Could you just please stop my doing?
Fine. Whatever.
Just stop worrying about Asta and concentrate on your own chances.
Huh? But there's nothing for me to be worried about.
I totally made it into the Royal Knights, so I ain't sweating it one bit.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, Narnie, you're completely terrified, aren't you?
No way. Don't be stupid.
And cool.
All right, fine. I suppose I could make an exception this once.
To lift your spirits, I'll let you look at Marie's photograph for three and a half seconds.
I've got a way better idea. Spore with me, Asta.
Huh?
I bet you're already feeling better.
Stop it. There's no way he's better.
Let me hit him with one full throttle attack.
I told you, you can't.
Oh, no. Charmy.
Hmm? What's gotten into you, girl?
I can't stop thinking about how cool Yuna was during that battle.
It's making my chest high in so much that I can barely swallow any food.
I've only eaten a fifth of it.
Yeah, you're fine.
You're not gonna say anything?
Oh, man. This is serious.
My incredible savior of sustenance.
My heart won't stop begging for you.
I'm pretty sure that's heartburn.
It looks like she's in bad shape, too.
I'll say.
But what can we do?
Hey!
How about a nice bath?
Hmm?
Huh?
Ah!
What up, boss?
What's this about about?
You're bound to cheer up after sweating it out in some piping hot water.
Come on. Let's go.
Thanks, but I don't really feel up to it.
Your captain orders you to, so quit your bellyaching and get in.
What'd I tell you?
A nice bath like this is just what the doctor ordered.
I guess so.
You're gonna get boiled alive if you do that one more time, you understand me.
How are you ladies doing? You warm enough?
It's perfect, Captain Yami. Thanks for asking.
I can't believe we're all sharing a bath. So embarrassing.
Oh, come on.
Damn, those chatty ladies sure are making a lot of racket.
Anyway, your situation really gets me thinking.
Huh? About what?
Shut your yap and I'll tell you.
It reminds me of a time when I just joined up with the Magic Knight Squad by the name of the Gray Deer.
Huh?
They're called the Aqua Deer now.
But this happened back when old Julius was their captain, so the name was different then.
That makes sense.
That's good. Now be quiet and listen to the story.
I've been doing some warrior training to beat myself up a bit, right?
It's story time all of a sudden.
Shoot.
I got hungry, so I decided to try catching some fish.
But then, I could eat a horse right now. I'm so hungry.
Come on, I don't have all day now.
Bite the damn thing.
Gotta catch something.
Gotcha.
Perfect.
You stole the bait.
Fishing is a breeze out on the open sea, but all this fiddly stuff really isn't my style.
Yep, I'm gonna starve to death.
This is Shakedown?
If you're looking for a fight, you've found one.
But being hungry tends to make me irritable, so I wouldn't expect a lot of mercy if I were you.
Here you are.
Forgive the intrusion, Sir Magic Knight, but you look like you could use something to eat.
You didn't put poison in these or anything, did you?
Of course not. That would be absurd.
Go on. Have some.
Well, I am kind of starving.
If you don't mind, we'd be happy to give you more in exchange for hearing our plea.
Is that something you would consider, Sir?
Sure, why not?
You see, harvest time will soon be at hand, and we're fortunate to be expecting a bountiful crop this year.
Okay, good for you, I guess.
Not exactly.
Huh?
They're coming to take it away. We're not sure what to do.
Who's they?
Bandits, of course.
They wait until we gather the crops we so diligently grew and harvested.
Then they come along and steal everything from us before we even realize what's happening.
We've tried submitting an appeal with the royal capital, but it seems we're not the only ones having this problem, and they're a bit short-staffed.
A village like ours isn't a priority.
Okay, so you brought me here because you want me to put the herd on some bandits for you, is that it?
Not for nothing. We fully intend to provide all of your meals while you're here. Three a day!
How dare you? You've got a lot of nerve. A good magic knight deserves more than food for his services.
But we have no money. The bandits took last year's harvest as well, so we're utterly impoverished.
Even that bread we gave you comes from our secret supply.
I want naps, too. Meals alone won't cut it. I need my shut-eye, and that's final.
How about that? Either you accept my conditions, or I'm not going to help save your wimpy little village.
Sounds like we've got ourselves a deal then. Well, I guess I've had about enough to eat.
So I think I'll go take mine now.
Wait, magic knight! I'm afraid we never had the opportunity to ask for your name.
It's Yami. Yami Sukihiro.
I'm kind of disappointed.
What's the matter, boss?
They've got another bumper crop this year. That really is too bad. We'll have to pull it all up by the roots.
I'm thinking it might be too heavy to carry back.
Oh, that's no problem. We got a guy who can use spatial magic. We'll bundle it and send it to the hideout.
Well, well, isn't that convenient.
Let's go! I'm sure those villagers will be waiting for us. Don't hesitate to crush them. Seal everything you can, no matter who gets in your way.
Yes, sir!
Let's see. Where do I begin? Which way leads to the granary? There? Should be straight ahead of you on the right.
Thanks.
Huh?
If I chase you away, you'll probably come back later. So I guess I better do something to make sure you never try to steal from this village again.
All right, that's one down.
Two down. Piece of cake.
And this bozo makes it three.
Eighteen, twenty, they just keep on coming.
How many are there?
What a surprise.
I see. They hired some two-bit magic knight to work security.
I take it you're the one who's in charge of this whole outfit?
You sure managed to scrape together plenty of small fries.
Working as a team, enough small fries can overpower the mightiest whale.
Just as it only takes one tiny termite to sink a massive galleon.
Now, men, let's teach this fool that there's strength in numbers.
A reward for whoever can kill him first.
Right!
Huh. They're not really a threat by themselves.
But there's too damn many of them.
What's the plan?
Well, not much else to do,
but cut you down one by one.
Gotcha!
Okay, who the hell are you?
I'm not an enemy.
Weird shoes, weird pants, weird clothes, weird cape, and that mask. It's goofy as hell.
You say you're not, but you look pretty shady in that peacock costume of yours.
Yami, I believe your name was. Watch my back if you wouldn't mind.
Hey, wait. I remember telling you what my name was, pal.
Oh well.
This guy, he moves like he's able to read my mind or something.
Our key must be on the same wavelength.
No, what happened? How did the two of you take down so many?
Well, that's done.
Now there's just you!
Make a portal! Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Hey, shrimp. Why'd you stay here and let your boss get away? Huh?
The bandit's boss may have barely slipped through our fingers, but we did round up all of his underlings. They won't be attacking this or any other village for a long while.
You got that right. Now, you never did give me a clear answer. I think I'd remember if I met somebody like you, so how did you know my name?
Oh, yes, you did ask me that. The truth is, you're famous. The roughneck from a foreign land who was chosen to join the Grey Deer isn't easily forgotten about.
Uh-huh. All right, then tell me who you are.
Actually, I am also a member of the Grey Deer. Huh?
You see, my own missions tend to take place in the Royal Capitals, so you and I have never crossed paths before this. Today's assignment just happened to be near here.
Yeah, now that you mentioned it, I did hear something about a newbie with a stupid mask joining up, so that must have been a good idea.
Yeah, that's a good idea. That's a good idea.
You think it's stupid? This mask was a gift from someone special, so that kind of hurts.
From someone special, huh? Well, it was sweet of them to give you a gift and all, but it's still ridiculous. Who the hell was it?
Who indeed?
Thank you, Sir Yami. Now, our humble village can prosper again.
We appreciate all your help, Sir Yami. You've protected our harvest for years to come.
Hey, don't worry about it. I mean, I did get myself a good meal out of this, after all. Take care.
Take care.
You want a bite of this bread?
That's alright, thank you. You were the person the village hired. I believe you should reap the rewards.
Suit yourself.
Where are you off to next?
I'm headed back to training. Feel free to join me.
Sounds nice. I'm sure things can be exciting with you around. But I must decline. I have a mission of my own I need to attend to. I'll bid you farewell and be on my way. Best of luck.
But you know, even though we have different goals now, I suspect we'll walk the same path in the future.
Just what path is that?
Sounds good. I guess that makes you my rival.
I intend to become the captain of the Magic Knight squad. Before you do, that is.
Yeah, right. You'll never beat me.
Then it's a contest. Let's see who gets there first.
Hey! Wait a minute, Mask Boy. You never got around to telling me your name.
Oh, right. It's William Vonges.
I should have known. Your name is as weird as your outfit.
We'll meet again, Yami.
Yeah, see ya.
All right. Time for me to get going, too.
That's it. That's the story of how I met that Masked Goofball.
And the first time he and I fought side by side.
After that, these two Magic Knights shared a friendly rivalry that continued for several years to come. Even to this very day.
after that was great.
Oh
Closer to it
Vongeance is a mouthful
Hey
Wait a minute mask boy
You never got around to telling me your name
Oh, right
It's William Vongeance
What's the last name?
It's Vongeance
All right, Vongeance
No, Vongeance
Von Schnellzer?
That's it all
Huh, uh, start over
I'd like that
Is it Vongeance?
Not at all
Listen closely
My name's Vongeance
Sounds like a shampoo
Well, I do try to take care of my hair
After that, these two magic knights shared a friendly rivalry that continued for several years
We get it!
Sorry
Man, sharing stories about my squad mates from the old days is starting to make me feel kind of sentimental
I was young back then too, you know
Black Clover page 86
Yami and Vongeance
I mean, I'm only 28
I'm still a spring chicken
Does it matter?
What's the correcting?
werde
aks
About that
Is coming in
Half a time
Up to the tern
We're not oh
No
Everyone
anyone
Loved